what's up everyone I'm AJ Brown and I'm
here to show you how to train like an
NFL wide receiver for the Super Bowl
long down the left side ground right in
the pocket he's got a 38 yd
completion at the age of 15 I started
working out I wasn't too fun of it but
you know I started started doing it and
as I got older and I grew it became
fun the advice that stuck with me is
from my trainer today uh Joey Gario and
that goes back into saying uh doing that
one extra rep but to really train
yourself you know don't just do the rep
um in the waight room just cuz it's what
it says No actually that's that's your
game time moment and so you need to lock
in and you know put everything you have
in these moments and and so you can try
to get the the max ability and step out
on the
field we're going to start with Kaa
power squats four sets three reps
[Music]
I'm trying to be explosive as I can here
in this video so he can translate on the
field with me coming off the ball and
just really just running you know uh
working my lower body legs
[Music]
glutes as a receiver the most important
muscle group I would definitely say the
lower body the glutes the handam me the
quads the ankle Mobility I want to say
really from your waist down because so
much goes into it and you're running
you're cutting you're putting your foot
in the ground you're stopping you're
starting you're running as fast as
possible and you stopping as fast as
possible so the lower body is so
important and you have to take care of
and you have to train really well next
up hamstring rotation three sets five
reps here is just really simple just
trying to work on the hamstring
flexibility lower body upper body uh
flexibility that just translate with
everything because without my hamstrings
and I can't do anything so
[Music]
next up we got kaer anti rotation press
three sets eight
reps it's just really self-explanatory
just just a press you know uh working
upper body that movement you know that
translate with me when I'm blocking get
my hands on guys and you know driving
them off the
ball I like to box a lot it helps on the
football field it translate because of
the cardio I do in the boxing I do it
for one that I fell in love with the
sport but also that I never get tired
it's just another way of I can do cardio
without putting a lot of stress on my
joints and you know just to stay
active next up is dumbbell bench press
four set five reps you can increase the
weight if you want to now I I do I kind
of get carried away actually cuz you
know I like to look good you know uh but
it it translate on the field with with
everything with hand fighting at the
line of scrimmage or me me just being
physical in between my routes and you
know making sure I have the room to
catch the ball fighting off guys it's
just that's
everything I don't have a favorite body
part to work out but I would say just
upper body you know I'm big strong I
like to look good you know feel good and
you know uh intimidate people
so next up hip thrust three sets of
eight
reps it's one of my favorite exercises
because it helps out with everything you
know we can't run unless our glutes are
firing and we most definitely We Can't
Stop without our glutes are firing so
that's just something that I'm trying to
strengthen and and make sure I can be
explosive that goes into the explosive
category that I do on a
daily me and Devonte workout is is
different but kind of similar in some
ways he may go lighter and sometimes I
go lighter and sometimes I go heavier
but as the season progress we all tend
to lower our weight because it's just
not smart thing to do and you have to
learn to manage that and I feel like we
have have done a great job in the weight
room to manage what what works best for
us next up single leg extensions three
sets of eight
reps one of my favorites that I like to
add in to make sure everything is is
working accordingly um my lower half so
it's really quad dominant and making
sure my quad is strong because my quad
is strong and my knee is good and it it
goes all the way down to my ankor so
everything works up everything's in a
straight line and that is a target area
that I'm going to focus because I have
to stop at full speed and these are my
[Music]
brakes next up ker Bell swings we got
four sets of six
reps I like to go heavy on these
extremely
heavy working glutes hammies again this
is something I'm going to keep targeting
because as a receiver I'm running I'm
stopping and and it's again it's one of
my favorite exercises cuz it's real
simple to do real easy and uh I can go
as heavy as I want to and you know but
make sure you do it correctly cuz you
don't want back
[Music]
PRS that's what it looks like to train
like an NFL wide receiver for the Super
Bowl I hope this helps the next time you
get in the gym